gucomics.com 2016-11-30

# GU Comics by: Woody Hearn

**Privacy Policy** ( Last Updated: 8/3/12 )

GU Comics makes every effort to safeguard the privacy of our users. And only collects information on an opt-in basis. That is to say, we collect information about our users only after they have been informaed as to what information we are collecting, how that information will be used, and they have agreed to submit the information we request. GU then only uses this information in the manner prescribed by the opt-in message. Where we do make every effort to link only those sites with similar privacy policy ideals, we can not control the activities of of sites not owned by GU Comics thus our Privacy Policy does not apply once you've followed a link away from our websites.  

**Cookies**  
Cookies are set by the GU forums and opt-in portions of the main GU website for the purposes of determining your login status and/or uphold preferences you've set that alter how you view the site. Methods for deleting GU set cookies are typically clearly defined on a page linked from the area where the cookie was set. The only exception are those cases where cookies are used in conjunction with voting or contest entries to help limit multiple submissions from the same user.

**Personal Information**  
In those cases where items, rewards, prizes, etc. are given away via the GU site, GU often requires an active email address be submitted so that "winners" can be informed that they have indeed won. Personal emails are not stored on the GU site in any form accessible by outside sources. And are not redistributed for any reason. When a winner is notified only then are they asked to provide a valid street address where their prizes can be sent. GU avoids direct access to this information when/where ever possible, preferring instead to let the company, distributor, third party collect the data. In these cases GU has no control over the third party's privacy policy.

**IP Addresses**  
The GU main site collects IP addresses on those occassions where the information is pertinent to limiting multiple submission to surveys, giveaways, etc. or is required to help create a unique identity for users that are participating in GU controlled auctions and the like. This information is not stored in any manner accessible by outside sources and is not given out for any reason.

**Information Collected From Minors**  
GU and its affiliated sites are considered to be PG-13. And special care is taken to protect those individuals indicating that they are younger than 13 years of age. In most cases users stating that they are not 13 or older are excluded from participating.

**Third Party Access to Personal Information**  
We only provide personal information to third parties in those cases where we specifically inform users as to how their personal information will be distributed and for what reasons. To date, GU has only given personal information to third parties for the purposes of delivering the winnings/purchases for giveaways and/or merchandise sells. GU does not store this information by any means that are accessible by third party sources not specifically associated with the sell/giveaway. GU can not control the practices of any company not directly controlled by GU.

GU uses third-party advertising companies to serve ads when you visit our Website. These companies may use information (not including your name, address email address or telephone number) about your visits to this and other Web sites in order to provide advertisements about goods and services of interest to you. If you would like more information about this practice and to know your choices about not having this information used by these companies, go to:  
<http://www.networkadvertising.org/managing/opt_out.asp>

**Further Questions**  
If you have additional questions about GU's privacy policy or how information is being collected, stored, or used for a specific giveaway, contest, auction, etc. please email:  
woody at gucomics dot com
